(Amy:)Oh, I'm not
confused at all.
(Amy:)You're like a sexy toddler.
(Sheldon:)I don't know
how to process that.
(Sheldon:)I do.
♪ Amy and Sheldon
sitting in a tree ♪
♪ K-I-S-S-S-S-I-N-G. ♪
(Penny:)That's too many S's
for "kissing."
(Bernadette:)Not if they're doing it
for a long time.
(Penny:)Sheldon... have you
ever kissed a girl?
(Sheldon:)Other than my mother,
my sister and my Mee-Maw, no.
(Sheldon:)But in the interest
of full disclosure,
(Sheldon:)I was once on a bus
(Sheldon:)and had to give
mouth-to-mouth resuscitation
(Sheldon:)to an elderly nun who passed out
from heat exhaustion.
(Sheldon:)Every year I get
a Christmas card from her,
(Sheldon:)signed with far
too many X's and O's.
(Bernadette:)That doesn't count.
(Bernadette:)Aren't you even
a little curious?
(Penny:)Yeah, you're a scientist--
where is the curiosity?